Guide to the Roy E. Huffman Papers1923-1990
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Missouri Basin Survey Commission - materials (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Montana Academy of Sciences (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Montana Annual Review of Public Affairs - proposal (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Montana Committee for the Humanities (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Montana Conservation Council (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Montana Energy Advisory Council (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Montana Farmer Stockman - correspondence and proposed Huffman articles (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Montana Historical Society (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Montana - miscellaneous magazines (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Montana State University - administration (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Montana State University - alumni (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Montana State University - Alumni Speech (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Montana State University - Blue and Gold Award (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Montana State University - Challenge Project (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Montana State University - faculty (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Montana State University - financial (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Montana State University - new degrees (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Montana State University - research (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Montana State University - research press coverage (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Montana State University - retirement (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Montana State University - role and scope (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Montana State University - 75th anniversary symposia (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Montana State University - students (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Montana State University - travel vouchers, 1968-1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Montana Water Congress (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Montana Water Development Association (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Museum of the Rockies (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Museum of the Rockies - Homestead Project (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Museum of the Rockies - Kirk Hill Nature Area (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Museum of the Rockies - newspaper clippings (Box 14, Folder 25)
- National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (Box 15, Folder 1)
- National Forests (Box 15, Folder 2)
- National Science Foundation paper on wind energy (Box 15, Folder 3)
- National Science Foundation proposed grant (Box 15, Folder 4)
- National seminar on "Implications of Agricultural Adjustments" (Box 15, Folder 5)
- NATO Senior Fellowships in Science (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Natural resources (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Natural Resources Journal - correspondence and proposed Huffman articles (Box 15, Folder 8)
- New Mexico College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts consulting assignment (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Newspaper clippings, reprint articles and clipped articles not in specific files (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Northern Plains Resource Council (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Northern Plains Soil and Water Research Center - Sidney, Montana (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Northern Tier Pipeline news clippings (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Northern Rockies Foundation - Jerry Calvert proposal (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Northwest Association of Secondary and Higher Schools - Accreditation Team (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Northwest Franchises, Inc (business venture) (Box 15, Folder 16)
- "Omnibus" - suggested outline (Box 16, Folder 1)
- "Omnibus" - Section 1 citations (Box 16, Folder 2)
- "Omnibus" - Section 2 citations (Box 16, Folder 3)
- "Omnibus" - Section 3 citations (Box 16, Folder 4)
- "Omnibus" - Section 4 citations (Box 16, Folder 5)
- "Omnibus" - Section 5 citations (Box 16, Folder 6)
- "Omnibus" - Section 5A citations (Box 16, Folder 7)
- "Omnibus" - Section 8 citations (Box 16, Folder 8)
- "Omnibus" notes - p 1-234 (Box 16, Folder 9-11)
- "Omnibus" - National Archives citations and notes not included in section 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Legal descriptions (Box 16, Folder 13)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Cloverleaf - summary (Box 16, Folder 14)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Comanche - summary (Box 17, Folder 1)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Richland - summary (Box 17, Folder 2)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Rosebud - summary (Box 17, Folder 3)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Wiota and Taiyan - summary (Box 17, Folder 4)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms: Yanktonai - summary (Box 17, Folder 5)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms - Elmer Starch memo, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms - Elmer Starch miscellaneous suggestions (Box 17, Folder 7)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms - Elmer Starch recordings (Folder Recordings, Phonograph-record 1-10)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms - Rita McDonald interviews for Dr. Huffman (Box 17, Folder 8)
- "Omnibus" research - Fairway Farms - Rita McDonald follow-up research (Box 17, Folder 9)
- "Omnibus" research - M.L. Wilson (paper by Merrill Burlingame) (Box 17, Folder 10)
- "Omnibus" - untitled rough draft manuscript, pp 1-359 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
- Oregon Graduate Center evaluation by Northwest Assn. of Schools and Colleges (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Orth, John C. - application forms and vita (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Outlook conference papers (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Over-the-Hill Administrative Council (informal social club) (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Overhead costs (research programs) (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Paradise Dam (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Patents (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Peace Corp - Columbia (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Penn, Raymond J. (Box 18, Folder 13)
- People and property rights (Box 19, Folder 1)
- People to People - China, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- People to People - registrations and deposits (Box 19, Folder 3)
- People to People - responses (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Personal memorabilia and papers - commencement announcements, calendar, etc. (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Planning Seminar, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Population statistics (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Preliminary and progress reports - Buford, Trenton grazing area (Box 19, Folder 8)
- President of Montana State Univ - Roy E. Huffman - application, vita, endorsements, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Presidential Search Committee (MSU), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Presidential Search Committee (MSU), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Production potentials (Montana agriculture) (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Programs of conferences, conventions, seminars, etc. (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs Forum, 1973 November 19-20 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Public Land Law Review - conference presentation manuscript and correspondence (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Public land trades and sales - newspaper clippings (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Public service (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Publication requests, 1946-1951 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Publishers - correspondence (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Pullman meeting - Washington State University - Department of Architecture, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Range Management - Annual meeting, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Reclamation - meeting, 1966 January (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Reclamation, Bureau of - correspondence and attachments, 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Reclamation Association - Montana (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Reclamation Association - National (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Reclamation - Strip mined lands (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Registrar and Treasurer, Montana State University, 1946-1952 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Renne, Roland R. (President's Office), Montana State University, 1945-1952 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Reprints of speeches, presentations and papers for conferences, etc. by Roy E. Huffman (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Reprints of speeches, presentations and papers by colleagues and peers of Huffman (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
- Research (general) - loose handwritten notes (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Research (general) - bibliographies (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Research (general) - miscellaneous clippings of interest (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Research (general) - reprinted articles, speeches, etc. (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
- Research (general) - university bulletins, circulars, etc. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Research brochure for Montana State University research programs - topic offerings (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Research by Department (MSU) (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Research clippings on MSU and educational research problems (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Research fellowship proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Research Foundation (MSU), 1947-1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Research ideas (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Research Park (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Research reports, 1943-1947 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Resource allocation, Arlie House Conference notes (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Retirement correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- River Press - Fort Benton (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Rocky Mountain Institute for Policy Research, 1975 July (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Ronald Press Co. - correspondence with attachments (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Ronald Press Co. - royalty statements (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Rural Institutions Seminar, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Rural Progress Conferences, 1952 March - February (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Russia: everything related to trip, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Sagebrush Rebellion, newspaper and article clippings (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Saline seep (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Saudi Arabia agricultural projects (Box 23, Folder 4-7)
- Saunderson, Mont H. (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Science and Technology Governor's Committee (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Secretary of Agriculture requested report for Montana on "War Production Goals and Their Attainment", 1942 June (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Seminars on science and technology (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Sheridan, Richard G.: typed manuscript and alternate introduction of "Water, Water Everywhere but?: a study of the politico-administrative aspects of water development in Montana", 1968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Sigma Xi Club (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Small watersheds (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Social Security correspondence re James L. Huffman (father) (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Sodbusting - newspaper clippings (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Soil Bank (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Spring seminar - "Economic development and environmental values", 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Staff seminars, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Starch, Elmer A., correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Starch, Elmer A., correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Starch, Elmer A., correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Starch, Elmer A., rough draft of "Great Plains Renaissance: Essays" by Elmer A. Starch; edited by Thomas R. Wessell, chapters 1-10 (Box 25, Folder 3-13)
- Starch, Elmer A. - draft manuscript of 50 articles for "A Saga of the Sage" by Starch, parts of which were published as "Great Plains renaissance: essays" (Box 25, Folder 13)
- State Water Board, 1946-1951 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Statistics - miscellaneous for Montana, 1970s-1980s (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Sugar beet correspondence, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Sugar beet materials (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Swine growers conference, 1964 February 18 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Taeusch, Carl F. (Chief of the Agricultural Adjustment Administration), copies of correspondence about Northern Great Plains School, 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Taxation and taxes (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Teacher Retirement System, 1940s-1950s (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Tenure in Water research project, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Tietz, President William J., Jr., correspondence (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Tillage - newspaper clippings and article reprints (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Tree ring studies (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Tribune articles (financing university education), 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Types of farming - U.S. maps, 1930, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- University Council on Water Resources (UCOWR), 1965-1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Unused manuscripts - University of California Department of Agricultural Economics (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Upper Missouri Water Users Assn - correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- USDA: "Historical Album of Agriculture" (Box 26, Folder 18)
- USDA Task Force on Rural Development and Family Living, 1967-1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Valley Authorities (Tennessee, Missouri, Columbia), 1944-1950s (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Vice President for Research, correspondence, 1965-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Water Board - correspondence, 1951, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Water Board research proposal, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Water Center, 1964-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Water - Citizens' Conferences, 1967 September 8-28 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Water conferences information and articles (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Water issues - newspaper clippings and articles (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Water Law course - Mock Water Adjudication, 1982 Spring (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Water Law Symposium (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Water Resources Policy Commission (Federal), 1950-1951 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Water Resources Research Center (WRRC) minutes (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Water Resources Research Center (WRRC) research proposal (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Water Resources Research Institutes, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Water rights, newspaper clippings (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Water Use in Montana, Historical Society Symposium, 1976 November 4-6 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Western Agricultural Economics Association (WAEA), 1955-1971 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Western Farm Economics Association, 1946-1966 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Western Interstate Water Conferences, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Western Interstate Water Conference, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Western States Water Council, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Western Water Resources Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Western Wildlands Journal article (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Wiley Research Awards, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Wilson, M.L. - papers, correspondence and reprinted articles (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Wilson, M.L. - Wilson Chair of Agricultural Economics, MSU (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Wilson, M.L. - Wilson Distinguished Lecture Series (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Wilson, M.L. - Wilson Symposium - correspondence, arrangements, papers, 1967 July 25-27 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Wilson, M.L. - Wilson Symposium - preliminary manuscript #1, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Wilson, M.L. - Wilson Symposium - preliminary manuscript #2, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Wind energy - Fred Davison (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Wind Reel (Curt Phillips) - development, correspondence, patent and legal papers (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Wisconsin - University of Wisconsin correspondence, papers for PhD program, 1949-1952 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Wisconsin - University of Wisconsin Press - papers and draft copy of thesis (Box 29, Folder 5-8)
- Worrall, Ted E.J. - correspondence on acquiring his Farm Machine Library for MSU (Box 29, Folder 9)
- "Yearbook of Agriculture, 1955" - correspondence, manuscript and related papers (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Yellowstone water reservations - personal papers and correspondence (Box 29, Folder 11)